Brother, I've got a snake. Brother,
come quickly.
Brother, I can't. Brother, come quickly. Sister, come quickly. Brother, I've got a snake. Grandpa, what kind of snake is it? Brother, look at that snake. Grandpa, I took a
snake for Tulsi and ate it.
Hurry up and buy it. Don't you have
anything? Chew it well. Chew it quickly.
Uncle, Tulsi took a snake and ate it.
Tulsi, if you get a snake, do you know what it is?
[Music]
The hospital doesn't need everything.
It will cost.
What's up, brother?   Did
you take Perusa with you?
[Music]
Hey, what kind of snake skin is this?
Many snakeskin.
Grandpa,
what a bad time.
[Crying] I don't know
what kind of snake it is, Dad.
My brother is looking for it.
Grandpa can't see what kind of snake it is.
But there was a good snake charmer in that place
.
Grandpa,
if you think of a good snake, you've got it right
.  The water snake came
here and gathered the whole town.
There is no water snake.  Even if it's a cut and paste,
they'll still gather like this.  That's right, who
brought so many people here?
I'm the one who sent a
voice message to my sister on our family WhatsApp group, and
everyone came and got
shocked.  It
hurts like that, Grandpa. Why don't you go to
court and say that you shouldn't run a white shop? Oh my God,
what will they do with this? In the
Acharya Dev Bhavan
matter, not one petition has been filed against you, but five or
six petitions have been filed.
What do we say on our side?  The
wine shop only opens at 12 noon.
What does he say to that?  No, he's
running around the block at 6 in the morning.
What do we say to that?  We
don't have wine shops and bars open after 10pm.  What does he say to that?   He only
becomes extremely active after 10 o'clock at night.  They sit on the
school grounds, completely bewildered, not knowing where to put the goods they buy at the night market
.
He said something more than this.  So,
take a plastic drinking glass and
mix it with water.  That's what makes you gargle
, that's what
makes you vomit.  Do you remember when
you had a banner saying "Diwali offer" and said that
whoever drinks fulla for more than ₹1000, they would give him a
fridge, TV, and
grinder in a jiffy
?
He filmed all of this and showed it
to the judges
.  He put the film bag on the bottom and said, "
Arum Ponnu."  What can you
do, uncle?
What has he been doing for so long?
Why are you getting tense now?
What is the verdict now? They have said that you
should not set up a wine shop in the town.
I will
give you a good idea.
We will put the wine shop and bar outside or in the village.
Our citizens are leaving without having to
borrow from the sharecropper to drink
.  Besides, no matter
what case we file, we
cannot stop our income.
Hey, the
rent he charges for running a wine shop is 5,000 baht a day.
We are proud to have a wine shop in our area.
This is what
my groom had a dream about
.  He runs this bar, he runs a
wedding hall, he runs a bar, he runs all this for the sake of
honor. He's just trying to take
your honor and he's just trying to steal it
like a scoundrel, so that's honor.
Arum Ponnu Petition Paraman.
What brother?
My brother will come home in the morning and see my father
.   It's a
good thing to be invisible, isn't it?
Oh, tell me, uncle, we want to talk about the Tulsi ritual
.  What are you
going to do, what did I say?
Uncle, you have to show them what you're afraid of,
uncle.
Hey, isn't this your hometown?   Don't
think about cutting down on unnecessary problems.
Uncle,
first of all, I'll ask them to leave their great-grandfather Arunathiya alone
.  Let's
see then.   I don't get
angry.  [Laughter]
What did you say?   I don't know
anything.
Comedy comedy.
Yo, is CPR good?
What is basil?
Is there a lock that shows what the CBI sees if asked?
Oh, there you are.
Store character lock.
The collector did not follow the order and wrote a shop note
[Laughter]
Again, the joke
[Music]
A future collector, you are going to break the coconut
Hi, my dear, how are you,
Collector, mother, you are from Chennai
Okay, okay,
uncle,
what's that, grandma?   I have
bought everything you need for the Tulsi ritual myself
.  PM agreed.
CM, do you agree?   Let's
make the ceremony special, Uncle
.  Did your brother agree?   The
nanny and her daughter had to
go to the ceremony because they had done so much for them.
When is the ceremony?   On the
third day, at six o'clock in the evening,
they will serve dinner.   If the uncle
insists on holding the wedding of the groom himself after the sister-in-law's ceremony,
he can be beaten.
Uncle's cough is getting worse and worse
.  Boil a glass of tea and blow it out
.
Eat and
put on some old sothu, Papa.
Hey Mundrikottai
Mapila uncle, let's fight to
make Mangoni the collector and make the sirens in our town come, let's
fight, let's fight, let's make it come,
Mapila,
oh wait, uncle,
what if I put my signature here in that green color
?   It will
be green.
Uncle, you must be very proud of your family.   Please don't let
anyone disturb you,
groom.
Whatever is written in your head, that's what
happens, uncle.  Just think about how well it's
written in your head.   If you
think about it, the
child has been
born in Munthirikottai. Look, I'll go and
come back when I'm free.
Mom,
go and bring your brother and your mother
.  They
won't let me have a cup of coffee.
What's the matter, brother? Did
you tell me to come? You've
brought everyone here, but you're just asking me
what service we're doing here for a security guard.
It's the road that goes to school,
ladies, you can't go that way. Not
only that, but two people on a
bike are supplying food 24 hours a day, from weddings to
weddings.  Is that so?
115 quarters are ₹150, that's
eggs, a side dish of chickpeas and
other
things, they are being served hot. They are lying in the assembly, they are not allowed to put it in a
bottle like that, they are not allowed to break it. Do you
know how many people come to the doctor? Now,
Mapli, you are very much at enmity with the
village, you don't want enmity with anyone, what are
you doing in politics? Why are you fighting for
good? Why do you want to do politics
[music]? We only talk about the problems on the way, we don't talk about the dangers, we only
ask about the mistakes on the way.
Half of the people here are
reluctant to do good because they are being asked to do good by holding a public meeting and asking if it is a tax on politics.
What the hell,
look at all the money flying in the sky.
Who gets married so that everyone can come and congratulate them?  I'm getting
married because of a relationship.  The groom's uncle's
wedding,
yes, the wedding,
I'm putting all the vegetables on it, and I'm
putting vegetables on the side.   Is
n't it special?
Why is there no Vishanka Shettam?
Hey, sister, are you okay?
Oh, are you okay?
Are you okay, why are you
taking
so long?  There is some work
.  What is that?  He's right here,
okay, okay, go inside.
Hey,
mother, uncle,
are you coming late like this to a wedding at home?
That's why you're here, if you
come home a little earlier, that's okay, partner.
What does my coming have to do with your coming
?
What's the point of having a baby?
Dad, I'm here,
how is this boy?
Okay, why?
Tulsi said, "
My brother,
your wife, won't cheat on me. Is
my partner thinking the same thing?" "
Come on, girl, what are you
talking about?" "Your father is looking for you. Come on, let's go
together. Don't let him talk.
I also want to tie a wedding saree like this
."
Partner, can we go and get a nice maroon color one for 10,000 rupees from Kanchipuram?   I just
said I'll pay for the sari.  You feel
something.   They
wear Vej at the wedding, and I
wear Vevem.  The wedding is happening, and the wedding
preparations are also happening.   Let
it happen, let it happen.   I
think you all are trying to ruin my becoming a collector.
So, overall,
you don't want to ruin the little bit of respect the collector has
?
Okay, okay.
[Music]
You'll never laugh in real life again.
Why is this girl bowing her head like that?
When I tie the knot, my husband pays the price.   I will
sit upright like that.   If
the Ampalais are ashamed, let them
bow down.
Yes, partner, sit up straight.
That's how my grandmother should be.
Hello, I'm not talking to you.
I said it in general.  I'm not saying it in general.
I told you.  Dappa Pattner.
Wrong partner.
You have good timing, partner.
He's just like that in the timing,
isn't he your father?
Hey, green child, if you talk like this in front of me, I'll get
angry.   If
he talks to the child, he scolds him.  Shall we
talk to one of our children?   They are
going very fast, and the
colorful flowers are coming, and Prasant is whistling alone
.  What kind of groom?
Why not invite me to a wedding?   Don't worry
.
Okay, let that be all.  Why have I been
walking alone?   I am
going abroad.
Sir, I have ruined my legal career
.  Don't ruin a girl's life
.  Please
leave for abroad.
Hey, this is why you're not invited to the wedding
.   I
know you won't call.   I
came back to the door after hearing the noise and
ate my meal.  Even the food
was as bland as yours.
Hey, look, he's going to roll around with his mouth wide open
.   The
only crying at the wedding was that of these people crying, and
even if they had children to cry with, they
wouldn't have cried so much.  Full of sentimental scenes
.
[Laughter]
We're the ones who are ruining the whole town
.  They were planning a wedding,
packed a van, and headed to Rameswaram
.
Yes, if they tease you, they will
scold you.  Dad, go to your house
.
What's the point of scolding him?
Did you marry your sister to tie her up? Or did you marry us too for our
parents' plan?
Yes, I
can't come to the wedding. I can't even call and say
goodbye and congratulate you.
Oh,
that's all your love. I don't think about it at all. I thought it was love,
but I
thought you wouldn't talk to me.
I also thought that you shouldn't even talk in this life.
But what are you doing?
Love is a disgrace to those who have bad reputations.
Hey, what's on your mind
?   I've been
thinking about you.   If
you had them,
how much would I have?
Ask your father how much he has coughed.
Who do you think our father is?
He is my father-in-law.
Who is our mother and our aunt then?
My mother has done everything for
you.  Blackcurrants, milk,
and a four-pound
country chicken.   What's up, we're having a
party for my sister
.  We all buy and return the goods and
leave.
No way,
do you know how our father raised us?   A
partner who has never lived and seen.
Hey now [music] I'm
so happy you called me, you know?
We were happy then too.
Tell him that PK is happy too.
Is the big Kenyan named PK also there?  [Laughter]
How come
no one in Asia can laugh as bad as him?
[Laughter] I'm
not sleeping, Grandpa.
How can I sleep? When you talk like this, I don't scold you
like I used to.
That's maturity, a well-read kid.
All these are not qualifications to become a collector
.  No one can make you happy like your own
.  No
one can make you suffer like your own
.
Hey, why don't you go and feed your relatives
?
Grandpa, we'll
throw a proper feast for our sister-in-law and the groom tomorrow.
Songwriter, brother.
Hey, is there something wrong with Tulsi's house
?  Did her husband
beat her?   If
you hit me, I'll
go to the Panchayat.
Then I'll go all out.  Oh my dear,
[Music] Don't just come here and lay your hands on my sister today
.  Why was I having a
hard time?  It will be
difficult for us to leave you.  Don't climb.
Good afternoon.
Hey, Ainara, your grandmother went and
brought your brother back.
[Music]
Come on, brother, I'm here.
How could you let Tulsiya go home when there was a big house in that house
?
Tulsi went inside the house and drove to Kochi.
This must be the last time she comes to our house
.
Hey, man, pull that thing and lock it.
Where is the interview?
Where did the gifts come from?  Tulsi should not
come to my mother's house even if she is a coach.   It is
important
not to sing the Purana of the house you entered.  Our mother is like this,
our brother is like that.   If he had
brought a stick to beat me, I would have taught him a
lesson.   If we
sit down and talk clearly,
there is no problem that cannot be solved here.  Why do
n't we just sit and talk?  Okay, uncle.
Okay,
brother, come on, brother.  No, that's okay,
sometimes life is
much easier than expected
.  Sometimes it's
better than expected.  Even if it's a little bit okay,
it will all be okay one day
.  This [music] is
not just for girls, it's for boys too.   If he
puts on a coat, he will look just
like Gopinath.
Please forgive Tulsi, the groom, if I said anything wrong.  Don't do anything your uncle wants
.
You made the action [music] emotional.
He is a big guy, don't hide the rope,
you don't have a son, think of him as
your daughter.
Oh, I'm not coming, I'm not coming, uncle,
what's the point?
Hey, driver, don't shoot the car, don't shoot the machine, partner,
where there is no partner, wo
n't I become a collector for life?
Alas!  Why are you throwing away such a big lump?
What will happen to my husband then?   You,
Koppan, are the ones who said this.
Which one?  Who threw all this stuff away?
Your person is the king.   Is
this the line?  Please
stay on the line for a minute.  Not saying anything.
Oh
Tulsi,
she's the one you're going to tie [music].   Have
you said everything within that?  That's a guy, hey what
[music] nonsense, I'll
hold his mouth and tear it open.
Oh, does she live nearby?  Hey, if
I thought about it, I would make whatever you thought
happen.  Is it
Alappuzha?  I'll play [music] later
.  Tell me now, did you say that I will
never become a collector
?  Say yes or no.
No, when did I tell Tulsi that?   You
said it yourself, there
was even a giant nearby.  It's quiet.  It was the
Almighty who said it.  He
said it wouldn't even be a compound in the collectorate.
Wait,
hello, Collector,
when are you going to do that green signature?
You were the one who said I wouldn't become a collector
.
Oh my, when did I say that?
You said it yourself.
You can become a collector, but I can build a stone
.
I said it out of emotion, brother.
Brother, when did I tell
you to stay by my side?  Maybe
Tulsi said, "
Brother Devuda,
you're the only one who's been listening to the phone,
who else can say?"
First, tell me who is on the line right now
.  [Music] I'll tell you
who said it later.
Anyone can say whatever they want.   If
you say so yourself, how can you
act like this, even with your good partner, Savitri?   Did
you fail the exam?  You hid it from me
.  I told Tulasi in that meeting
.  Would
I have told you if I had known it would be like this?   I don't know what level
your actions are at
.  Shut
up and go outside.
Hey
partner, do you know I
saved [music] as Mango IAS
?
So, brother,
you should always give importance to me
.
Hello, hello, we are all online.
Why do you keep quiet about family problems
?
Okay, I'm gone.
This is all a joke.
That's some cross dog.
Where are you now?  [Music] I
trust in the place where I pour the milk
.   Let me
talk,
okay, I'm gone,
brother.